KOSTADIN KELJTANOSKI

CERTIFIED LARAVEL DEVELOPER | SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER | https://kelitanoski.github.io

Address

Arhiepiskop Dositej 129 7500, Prilep, R.Makedonija

Contact

keljtanoski@gmail.com +38978456945

E2

ABOUT ME

Software Engineer with 6+ years of professional experience, profound in all of the phases of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) for designing and building complex web applications and APIs. Perform business and technology analysis, system integration engineering, custom software development, support and maintenance, refactoring and re-engineering, unit testing and validation of services and solutions. Experienced in agile development and design of high volume and high quality software components and applications. Currently working with the Laravel Framework. Always thrilled to learn new stuff.



WORK EXPERIENCE

ZEROPLEX

March **2019 -** Present

Senior Software Engineer / Project Lead Laravel Developer

Working as a Senior Software Engineer, Project Lead Developer as part of the remote Laravel Team from Xessable. Leading an internal all in one CRM/EMP/HRM/ICT Project. Involved in all of the phases of SDLC, working closely with the Product Owner, creating day to day deliverables, architecting solutions, making extensive code reviews and executing throughout testing. Developing software solutions for various clients, creating RESTApis, custom Laravel packages, custom invoice module, writing API Documentation.

XESSABLE

March 2019 - Present

Senior Software Engineer / Project Lead Laravel Developer

Working as a Senior Software Engineer, Project Lead Developer. Guiding and mentoring the internal Xessable Laravel Team, providing feedback, problem-solving, managing and creating day to day deliverables and tasks for the assigned internal project, writing reports, estimations, executing code reviews and testing.

SMITH & ASSOCIATES

June **2018 -** March **2019**

Full Stack PHP Developer / Magento 1 & 2 CE & EE developer

Working as a Full Stack Magento 1 & 2 CE & EE Developer as part of the remote Magento Team from InterWorks, creating custom modules, widgets and plugins for Magento 2 EE, helping the remote DevOps team with creating and fixing Docker scripts for setting up the project environment. Implementing Task Runner - Grunt for improved workflow for Magento 1 project.

INTERWORKS

May **2018 -** March **2019**

Full Stack PHP Developer / Magento 1 & 2 CE & EE developer

Working as a Full Stack Magento 1 & 2 CE & EE Developer, creating custom modules, widgets and plugins for Magento 2 EE.

VOX TENEO

March **2016 -** May **2018**

Full Stack PHP Developer / Laravel / Drupal 7 & 8 / WordPress developer
Working as a Full Stack PHP Developer, handling multiple Drupal 7 & 8,
WordPress and Laravel 4 & 5 projects simultaneously

ASIDUS - BITOLA

March **2014** - December **2017**

Web Designer & Developer / Project Manager / PHP developer

March 2016 - December 2017 (Part time)

Working as a Freelance Contractor , Full Stack PHP Developer / Web Designer on multiple projects for local and international clients

March 2014 - March 2016 (Full time)

Working as a Full Stack PHP Developer / Web Designer on multiple projects for local and internation clients, working on the internal



DEVELOPER SKILLS

HTML5 / Bootstrap / Bulma / Magento 1 & 2 (Community and Enterprise Edition) Foundation CSS / LESS / SASS PHP / OOP PHP JS / jQuery Laravel Framework (TDD, DI) Grunt / Gulp / Webpack Drupal 7, 8 & Commerce Tailwind / Atomic CSS SQL / MySql CI / Jenkins RESTful API / 3rd party APIs ES / Vue|S Docker / Vagrant / VM Twig / Blade templating Kanban / SCRUM / Agile / JIRA **SOLID Principles** Ajax / JSON



LANGUAGES

WordPress

English French



CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Laravel Developer

Successfully completed the test requirements and demonstrated the knowledge and skills to be recognized as a Certified Laravel Developer.

Design Patterns

Date: April 14th 2020 - Does not expire



EDUCATION

"St. Clement of Ohrid" University, Bitola Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies (FIKT) Bitola,R.Makedonija Study program: COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

SOU Gimnazija MIRCHE ACEV- Prilep

Prilep, R.Makedonija Study program:Natural science and mathematics - A



SOCIAL LINKS



https://www.linkedin.com/in/keltanoski



https://github.com/k3dk https://github.com/keljtanoski



kostadin.keljtanoski



https://keljtanoski.github.io/